[
  {
    "type": "user",
    "members": [
      {
        "userID": 0,
        "userName": "Test User",
        "password": "password",
        "last105Score": 0,
        "last106Score": 5,
        "last220Score": 0,
        "last230Score": 0,
        "max105Score": 0,
        "max106Score": 5,
        "max220Score": 0,
        "max230Score": 0
      },
      {
        "userID": 1,
        "userName": "Bob",
        "password": "1234",
        "last105Score": 0,
        "last106Score": 0,
        "last220Score": 0,
        "last230Score": 0,
        "max105Score": 0,
        "max106Score": 0,
        "max220Score": 0,
        "max230Score": 0
      },
      {
        "userID": 2,
        "userName": "autumn",
        "password": "test",
        "last105Score": 0,
        "last106Score": 0,
        "last220Score": 0,
        "last230Score": 0,
        "max105Score": 0,
        "max106Score": 0,
        "max220Score": 0,
        "max230Score": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "course",
    "members": [
      {
        "courseID": 1,
        "title": "Introduction to Computer Science"
      },
      {
        "courseID": 2,
        "title": "Data Structures"
      },
      {
        "courseID": 3,
        "title": "Assembly Language Programming"
      },
      {
        "courseID": 4,
        "title": "Programming Languages"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "lesson",
    "members": [
      {
        "lessonID": 1,
        "courseID": 1,
        "header": "Introduction to Computer Science",
        "content": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet"
      },
      {
        "lessonID": 2,
        "courseID": 2,
        "header": "Data Structures"
      },
      {
        "lessonID": 3,
        "courseID": 3,
        "header": "Assembly Language Programming",
        "content": "lorem ipsum dolor sit amet"
      },
      {
        "lessonID": 4,
        "courseID": 4,
        "header": "Programming Languages",
        "content": "lorem ipsum dolor sit amet"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "quiz",
    "members": [
      {
        "quizzID": 1,
        "lessonID": 1,
        "numberOfQuestions": 5
      },
      {
        "quizzID": 2,
        "lessonID": 2,
        "numberOfQuestions": 5
      },
      {
        "quizzID": 3,
        "lessonID": 3,
        "numberOfQuestions": 5
      },
      {
        "quizzID": 4,
        "lessonID": 4,
        "numberOfQuestions": 5
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "members": [
      {
        "questionID": 1,
        "quizID": 2,
        "prompt": "What is the main difference between arrays and vectors?",
        "optionA": "Vectors have a fixed size, while arrays have dynamic size",
        "optionB": "Vectors can hold items of multiple types, while arrays cannot",
        "optionC": "Arrays can hold items of multiple types, while vectors cannot",
        "solution": "Arrays have a fixed size, while vectors have dynamic size"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 2,
        "quizID": 2,
        "prompt": "Which way to declare an array is CORRECT?",
        "optionA": "<code>myArr = [1, 2, 'a'];</code>",
        "optionB": "<code>int myArr;</code>",
        "optionC": "<code>char myArr = {'a', 'b', 'c'};</code>",
        "solution": "<code>int myArr(3);</code>"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 3,
        "quizID": 2,
        "prompt": "Which way to declare a vector is NOT CORRECT?",
        "optionA": "<code>vector<int> myVec = {1, 2, 3};</code>",
        "optionB": "<code>vector<char> myVec;</code>",
        "optionC": "<code>vector<int> myVec(3);</code>",
        "solution": "<code>vector<char> myVec = 'a';</code>"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 4,
        "quizID": 2,
        "prompt": "Given:<p id='code-block'><code>vector<int> myVec = {1, 2, 3};</p></code>\nHow do you add the element 5 to the end of myVec?",
        "optionA": "<code>myVec.add_el(5);</code>",
        "optionB": "<code>myVec += 5;</code>",
        "optionC": "<code>myVec.push(5);</code>",
        "solution": "<code>myVec.push_back(5);</code>"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 5,
        "quizID": 2,
        "prompt": "Given:<p id='code-block'><code>vector<int> myVec = {1, 2, 3};</p></code>\nHow do you remove the last element from myVec?",
        "optionA": "<code>myVec.pop();</code>",
        "optionB": "<code>myVec -= 5;</code>",
        "optionC": "<code>myVec.pop_back(5);</code>",
        "solution": "<code>myVec.pop_back();</code>"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 6,
        "quizID": 2,
        "prompt": "What makes a structure different from an array?",
        "optionA": "An array can change size, structure cannot",
        "optionB": "The values of structure elements can change, array values cannot",
        "optionC": "An array can hold mixed types, structures cannot",
        "solution": "Arrays hold same-type elements; structures hold mixed types."
      },
      {
        "questionID": 7,
        "quizID": 2,
        "prompt": "Given:<p id='code-block'><code>class Box { private:\n\t\tint height, length, width;\npublic:\n\tBox(int h = 0, int l = 0, int w = 0) {\n\t\theight = h;\n\t\tlength = l;\n\t\twidth = w;\n\t}\n\tdouble calcVolume() {\n\t\treturn height * length * width;\n\t}\n}</p></code>\nWhich of these code snippets contains an error?",
        "optionA": "<code>Box myBox();</code>",
        "optionB": "<code>Box myBox(1, 2, 3);</code>",
        "optionC": "<code>double volume = myBox.calcVolume();</code>",
        "solution": "<code>myBox.height = 3;</code>"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 8,
        "quizID": 2,
        "prompt": "What is the difference between public and private variables and functions in a class?",
        "optionA": "Private: cannot be changed, public: can be changed",
        "optionB": "Public: known to the user, private: secret",
        "optionC": "Private: only access outside class, public: can change outside class",
        "solution": "Private: access inside class. Public: access/change outside class",
        "isCode": 0
      },
      {
        "questionID": 9,
        "quizID": 2,
        "prompt": "Given:<p id='code-block'><code>class Box {\nprivate:\n\t\tint height, length, width;\npublic:\n\tBox(int h = 0, int l = 0, int w = 0) {\n\t\theight = h;\n\t\tlength = l;\n\t\twidth = w;\n\t}\n\tdouble calcVolume() {\n\t\treturn height * length * width;\n\t}\n}\nBox myBox(2, 3, 4);</code></p>\nWhat does myBox.calcVolume() return?",
        "optionA": "18",
        "optionB": "9",
        "optionC": "22",
        "solution": "24"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 10,
        "quizID": 2,
        "prompt": "When you declare a class or structure, you are creating a blueprint for a container that can hold a certain combination of elements. When you create an actual object from that blueprint, it is called a(n) _____ of that class or structure",
        "optionA": "container",
        "optionB": "model",
        "optionC": "iteration",
        "solution": "instance"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 11,
        "quizID": 3,
        "prompt": "Convert the following number from Decimal to Hexadecimal: 938324",
        "optionA": "0xF2469",
        "optionB": "0xE5153",
        "optionC": "0x259D5",
        "solution": "0xE5154"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 12,
        "quizID": 3,
        "prompt": "Convert the following number from Hexadecimal to Decimal: 0x6FA8D",
        "optionA": "624826",
        "optionB": "451608",
        "optionC": "623792",
        "solution": "457357"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 13,
        "quizID": 3,
        "prompt": "What is the appropriate suffix for this instruction, based on the operands: <strong>mov? %rsi, %rax</strong>    # ? should be",
        "optionA": "B",
        "optionB": "W",
        "optionC": "L",
        "solution": "Q"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 14,
        "quizID": 3,
        "prompt": "Convert the following number from Binary to Hexadecimal: 10000010010011111010001101111100",
        "optionA": "0x1AC295D3",
        "optionB": "0x2948BCE0",
        "optionC": "0x824D6E29",
        "solution": "0x824FA3BC"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 15,
        "quizID": 3,
        "prompt": "What command would you use to DECLARE a variable?",
        "optionA": ".bss",
        "optionB": ".define",
        "optionC": ".int",
        "solution": ".lcomm"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 16,
        "quizID": 3,
        "prompt": "What do you subtract/add by to convert ASCII values to numbers?",
        "optionA": "Whatever the Decimal value is for your number on the ASCII chart",
        "optionB": "Whatever your value is",
        "optionC": "0x3",
        "solution": "0x30"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 17,
        "quizID": 3,
        "prompt": "What symbol is used in x86-64 assembly to represent an immediate value?",
        "optionA": "#",
        "optionB": "%",
        "optionC": "@",
        "solution": "$"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 18,
        "quizID": 3,
        "prompt": "What symbol is used to indicate registers being used?",
        "optionA": "$",
        "optionB": "@",
        "optionC": "#",
        "solution": "%"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 19,
        "quizID": 3,
        "prompt": "Which is NOT an Assembly command?",
        "optionA": "add",
        "optionB": "sub",
        "optionC": "mov",
        "solution": "imult"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 20,
        "quizID": 1,
        "prompt": "Which of the following is used to display output in C++?",
        "optionA": "cin",
        "optionB": "printf",
        "optionC": "input",
        "solution": "cout"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 21,
        "quizID": 1,
        "prompt": "Which keyword is used to declare an integer variable?",
        "optionA": "number",
        "optionB": "float",
        "optionC": "string",
        "solution": "int"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 22,
        "quizID": 1,
        "prompt": "What does the 'cin' statement do in C++?",
        "optionA": "Displays output",
        "optionB": "Declares a variable",
        "optionC": "Ends a program",
        "solution": "Receives user input"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 23,
        "quizID": 1,
        "prompt": "Which control structure would you use to make a decision in a program?",
        "optionA": "for loop",
        "optionB": "do-while loop",
        "optionC": "function",
        "solution": "if-else statement"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 24,
        "quizID": 1,
        "prompt": "Which loop executes at least once regardless of the condition?",
        "optionA": "for loop",
        "optionB": "while loop",
        "optionC": "foreach loop",
        "solution": "do-while loop"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 25,
        "quizID": 1,
        "prompt": "Which function definition is correct in C++?",
        "optionA": "function greet() {}",
        "optionB": "def greet() {}",
        "optionC": "function greet[] {}",
        "solution": "void greet() {}"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 26,
        "quizID": 1,
        "prompt": "How would you define a function that adds two integers?",
        "optionA": "void add(a + b)",
        "optionB": "function add(int a, int b) return a + b;",
        "optionC": "int add(a, b)",
        "solution": "void add(int a, int b)"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 27,
        "quizID": 1,
        "prompt": "Which of the following is a correct array declaration in C++?",
        "optionA": "array numbers = [1, 2, 3];",
        "optionB": "int numbers[] = 1, 2, 3;",
        "optionC": "numbers int[3] = {1,2,3};",
        "solution": "int numbers[3] = {1, 2, 3};"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 28,
        "quizID": 1,
        "prompt": "Which header file is needed to use the 'string' type in C++?",
        "optionA": "#include <str>",
        "optionB": "#include <cstring>",
        "optionC": "#include <data>",
        "solution": "#include <string>"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 29,
        "quizID": 1,
        "prompt": "What will the following code output: cout << numbers[0]; with numbers[5] = {1,2,3,4,5}?",
        "optionA": "0",
        "optionB": "2",
        "optionC": "5",
        "solution": "1"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 30,
        "quizID": 4,
        "prompt": "What keyword do you use to declare a function in Python? ",
        "optionA": "Funct",
        "optionB": "Definition",
        "optionC": "Function",
        "solution": "Def"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 31,
        "quizID": 4,
        "prompt": "What is concatenation?",
        "optionA": "The keyword that declares a function",
        "optionB": "The javascript commands that creates a pop-up alert",
        "optionC": "Something to do with cats",
        "solution": "An operator that adds different data types together"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 32,
        "quizID": 4,
        "prompt": "What does the Regex command ^dog check for?",
        "optionA": "It checks that dog is not included in the user input",
        "optionB": "It checks for alphanumeric characters",
        "optionC": "It checks that given user input ends with dog",
        "solution": "It checks that given user input begins with dog"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 33,
        "quizID": 4,
        "prompt": "What does the regex command [a-zA-Z0-9] check for?",
        "optionA": "It checks that given user input includes 1 alphabetic character",
        "optionB": "It checks that given user input ends with a number",
        "optionC": "It checks that given user input is not alphanumeric",
        "solution": "It checks that given user input is alphanumeric"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 34,
        "quizID": 4,
        "prompt": "What does the line userName = input() do?",
        "optionA": "It prints user input to the screen",
        "optionB": "It only accepts input but doesn't store it anywhere",
        "optionC": "It only creates a variable for input",
        "solution": "It takes in user input and stores it in the new variable UserName"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 35,
        "quizID": 4,
        "prompt": "What is CSS's main functionality?",
        "optionA": "CSS pairs with Python to build webpages",
        "optionB": "CSS helps to create function definitions",
        "optionC": "CSS pairs with JavaScript to create interactive webpages",
        "solution": "CSS pairs with HTML to add style and design choices"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 36,
        "quizID": 4,
        "prompt": "What does the line print('Nice to meet you') do?",
        "optionA": "It declares a function definition",
        "optionB": "It checks for input",
        "optionC": "It stores data about the user",
        "solution": "It prints the line within the parenthesis to the user's screen"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 37,
        "quizID": 4,
        "prompt": "In HTML, what are headings in arrow brackets < > called?",
        "optionA": "H1",
        "optionB": "Body",
        "optionC": "Head",
        "solution": "Tags"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 38,
        "quizID": 4,
        "prompt": "What is Javascript's main functionality?",
        "optionA": "It navigates databases",
        "optionB": "It build webpages",
        "optionC": "It pairs with CSS to add style and design choices",
        "solution": "It pairs with HTML to create interactive webpages"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 39,
        "quizID": 4,
        "prompt": "what does the line: style type=''text/css'' do? ",
        "optionA": "It edits the margin size",
        "optionB": "It styles the font of the CSS",
        "optionC": "It changes the background color",
        "solution": "It tells the HTML that there will be upcoming stylistic CSS commands"
      },
      {
        "questionID": 40,
        "quizID": 3,
        "prompt": "What integers are hexadecimals made up of? ",
        "optionA": "0-15",
        "optionB": "A-E, then 0-9",
        "optionC": "0-9, then A-E",
        "solution": "0-9,then A-F"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "loginCheck",
    "members": [
      {
        "isLoggedIn": 1,
        "userID": 0
      }
    ]
  }
]